Archival Collective Bargaining Agreements File 6030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Telephone Wkrs. - Southwestern, 1945 (Box 242, Folder 20)
- Telephone Employees' Association, Upstate (NY), 1974 (Box 242, Folder 21)
- Upstate Telephone Employees' Association, 1977 (Box 242, Folder 22)
- Telephone Employees of Michigan, Federation of, 1947 (Box 242, Folder 23)
- Telephone Employees' Organization, 1951 (Box 242, Folder 24)
- Telephone Laboratories Employees Union (Bx 225), 1946 (Box 242, Folder 25)
- Telephone Organizations, United, 1959 (Box 242, Folder 26)
- Telephone Traffic Union, Upstate New York, 1952-1954 (Box 242, Folder 27)
- Telephone Traffic Union, 1974 (Box 242, Folder 28)
- Telephone Traffic Union (NY), 1956-1957 (Box 242, Folder 29)
- Telephone Traffic Workers, New England Federation of, 1958 (Box 242, Folder 30)
- Telephone Workers, Connecticut Union of, 1942 (Box 243, Folder 1)
- Telephone Workers, Int'l. Brotherhood of, 1949-1964 (Box 243, Folder 2)
- Telephone Workers of Delaware, United, 1943-1954 (Box 243, Folder 3)
- Telephone Workers of New Jersey, Commercial, 1959-1961 (Box 243, Folder 4)
- Telephone Workers of New Jersey, Ind., 1946 (Box 243, Folder 5)
- Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1962-1971 (Box 243, Folder 6)
- Box 225, 1971-1974 (Box 243, Folder 7)
- Tennessee Valley Trades and Labor Council - Agreements, 1940-1951 (Box 243, Folder 8)
- Texan Unions, Federated Ind., 1950 (Box 243, Folder 9)
- Textile Workers' Union, Ind., 1958-1966 (Box 243, Folder 10)
- Theatrical Protective Union, 1961-1965 (Box 243, Folder 11)
- Toms River Chemical Employees Union, Inc., 1962-1964 (Box 243, Folder 12)
- Tool and Die Makers Assoc. of Bulova Watch Co., 1962 (Box 243, Folder 13)
- Traffic Employees Association, 1965 (Box 243, Folder 14)
- Transit Workers Union of Hawaii, Ind., 1949-1951 (Box 243, Folder 15)
- Trico Workers Union, 1959 (Box 243, Folder 16)
- Uniformed Sanitation Men's Assoc., 1969 (Box 243, Folder 17)
- Union of Care Employees, 1959 (Box 243, Folder 18)
- Federation of University Employees, 1951-1953 (Box 243, Folder 19)
- Weberdorfer-Wills Employees' Assoc., Inc., 1953 (Box 243, Folder 20)
- Associated Welders of Western N.Y., Inc., 1961 (Box 243, Folder 21)
- Western States Service Station Employees' Union, 1959-1960 (Box 243, Folder 22)
- Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions, 1947-1970 (Box 243, Folder 23)
- Western Electric Employees Assn. (Bx 225), 1946 (Box 243, Folder 24)
- Weston Employees Union, 1963 (Box 243, Folder 25)
- W.H. Loomis Tale Corp. Employees' Ind. Union, 1950 (Box 243, Folder 26)
- Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, 1952 (Box 243, Folder 27)
- Wholesale Flower Trade Workers, Brotherhood of, Ind., 1957 (Box 243, Folder 28)
- Wesner- Rapp Employees' Ind. Union, 1959 (Box 243, Folder 29)
- Women's Protective Union, 1971 (Box 243, Folder 30)
- Workers' Council, 1955 (Box 243, Folder 31)
- Yerkes Laboratories Union, 1964 (Box 243, Folder 32)
- Zanesville Armco Indep. Org. Inc., 1956 (Box 243, Folder 33)
- Airline Pilots Association w/ Transworld Airlines, Inc. 1985 (Box 244, Folder 1)
- American Federation of Government Employees w/ U.S. Department of Justice, 1976 (Box 244, Folder 2)
- American Federation of Musicians of the U.S. Canada w/ Lionel Hampton Orchestra, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 3)
- American Federation of School Administrators w/ the Day Care Council of NY, Inc. 1981-1982 (Box 244, Folder 4)
- American Postalworkers Union, Nat'l. Assoc. of Letter Camers, Nat'l. Post Office Mail Handlers, Watchmen, Messengers and Group Leaders Division of the Laborers' International Union of N.A 1975- 1978 (Box 244, Folder 5)
- American Postal Workers Union, 1978-1981 (Box 244, Folder 6)
- Local 66 Architectural and Engineering Guild w/ Pennwalt Corporation 1974-1976 (Box 244, Folder 7)
- The Association of Harper and Row Employees w/ Harper and Row, Publishers, Inc. 1977-1980 (Box 244, Folder 8)
- Local 550 Bakery Drivers Union w/ Continental Baking Company, Inc. 1987-1991 (Box 244, Folder 9)
- Clothing and Textile Workers Union w/ The Raybestos Industrial Products Company 1980 (Box 244, Folder 10)
- District Council 1707 Community and Social Agency Employees Union w/ Day Care Council of New York, Inc. 1978-1979 (Box 244, Folder 11)
- District 1707 Community and Social Agency Employees Union w/ Louise Wise Services 1983-1985 (Box 244, Folder 12)
- District Council 1707 Community and Social Agency Employees Union AFL-CIO w/ University Settlement, Inc. 1992 (Box 244, Folder 13)
- District 65 Distributive Workers of America w/ Automated Labels and Forms, Inc. 1973 (Box 244, Folder 14)
- Local 1199 Drug, Hospital and Health Care Employees Union w' League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of New York 1989-1992 (Box 244, Folder 15)
- Education Association of Paramus w/ Paramus Board of Education 1977-1980 (Box 244, Folder 16)
- Faculty Federation of Somerset County College and Board Of Trustees of Somerset County College 1975-1978 (Box 244, Folder 17)
- Federation of Telephone Workers of PA w/ The Bell Telephone Company of PA 1980 (Box 244, Folder 18)
- Local 144 Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home and Allied Services Union w/ The Association of Private Hospitals Inc. 1985 (Box 244, Folder 19)
- The Independent Association of Publishers' Employees, Inc. w/ DOW Jones and Company Inc. 1987-1990 (Box 244, Folder 20)
- Insurance Workers International Union w/ John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company 1978 (Box 244, Folder 21)
- Insurance Workers International Union w/ Metropolitan Life Insurance Company 1978-1981 (Box 244, Folder 22)
- Insurance Workers International Union w/ Golden State Mutual Life Insurance Company 1969 (Box 244, Folder 23)
- Insurance Workers International Union AFL-CIO w/ The Prudential Insurance Company of America 1979 (Box 244, Folder 24)
- District 15 International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Local 571 w/ AM International, Inc. 1975 (Box 244, Folder 25)
- International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers w/ Teledyne Farris Engineering 1986 District 15 (Box 244, Folder 26)
- International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers w/ Trans World Airlines, Inc. 1983 (Box 244, Folder 27)
- International Association of Machinists w/ United Parcel Service, Inc. 1971-1974 District 15 Local 447 (Box 244, Folder 28)
- Local 167 of International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers w/ Wood Industries Inc. 1977-1980 (Box 244, Folder 29)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers w/ Associated Universities Inc. Brookhaven National Laboratory Local 2230, 1979- 1981 (Box 244, Folder 30)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers w/ Brooklyn Union Gas 1983-1986 (Box 244, Folder 31)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers w/ CBS, Inc. 1984 (Box 244, Folder 32)
- Locals 320 and 2218 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers w/ Central Hudson Gas and Electrical Corp. 1979-1981 (Box 244, Folder 33)
- Locals 320 and 2218 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers w/ Central Hudson Gas and Electrical Corp. 1983-1985 (Box 244, Folder 34)
- Locals 320 and 2218 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers w/ Central Hudson Gas and Electrical Corp. 1983-1985 (Box 244, Folder 35)
- International Brotherhood of Electric Workers w/ Consolidated Edison Company of NY, Inc. 1977-1980 (Box 244, Folder 36)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers w/ N.Y. Electrical Contractors Association Inc., and Association of Electrical Contractors, Inc. Local No. 3 1986 (Box 244, Folder 37)
- Local 2124 of International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers w/ The Okonite Company 1968 (Box 244, Folder 38)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers w/ Orange and Rockland Utilities, Inc. Local 503 1981 (Box 244, Folder 39)
- International Brotherhood of Security Personnel Officers and Guards w/ Episcopal Health Services 1992-1995 (Box 244, Folder 40)
- Int'l. Photographers of the Motion Picture Industries w/ Int'l. Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the U.S. and Canada, 1975 (Box 244, Folder 41)
- International Typographical Union w/ International Printing Trades Unions Comprising the International Allied Printing Trades Association 1969 (Box 244, Folder 42)
- International Union of Elevator Constructors w/ National Elevator Industry, Inc. 1977-1982 (Box 244, Folder 43)
- International Union of Elevator Constructors and Otis Elevator Co. 1990-1993 (Box 244, Folder 44)
- Local G8 International Union of Operating Engineers w/ Golden State Paper Company, Inc. 1979-1989 (Box 244, Folder 45)
- Local G8 International Union of Operating Engineers w/ Golden State Paper Company, Inc. 1985 (Box 244, Folder 46)
- Local Cartage Employees of Private, Common, Contract and Local Cartage Camers w. National Master Freight 1991-1994 (Box 244, Folder 47)
- District 65 National Council of Distributive Workers of America w/ Clay Adams 1973 (Box 244, Folder 48)
- National Treasury Employees Union w/ U.S. Customs Service 1980 (Box 244, Folder 49)
- National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees w/ League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of N.Y. 1978-1980 District 1199 (Box 244, Folder 50)
- National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees w/ League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of N.Y. 1980-1982 District 1199 (Box 244, Folder 51)
- N.Y. Hotel and Motel Trades Council w/ Hotel Association of N.Y.C., Inc. 1972 (Box 244, Folder 52)
- New York Maller's Union No. 6 w/ New York News, Inc. and The New York Times Company 1978-1981 (Box 244, Folder 53)
- N.Y. Mailer's Union No. 6 Printing, Publishing and Media Workers' Sector of the Communications Workers of America w/ the New York Times Company, 1987 (Box 244, Folder 54)
- N.Y.S. Nurses Association w/ The Maimonides Medical Center 1986-1988 (Box 244, Folder 55)
- N.Y. Typographical Union No. 6 w/ N.Y. News Inc. and New York Times Company 1984 (Box 244, Folder 56)
- N.Y. Typographical Union No. 6 w/ Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. 1983 (Box 244, Folder 57)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 8-651 w/ Gulf Oil Company 1979 (Box 245, Folder 1)
- Local 8-575 Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union w/ Merck and Co., Inc., 1978 (Box 245, Folder 2)
- Local Unions 1349, 1357, 1358, 1360, 1361, 1371 and 1393 w/ Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. 1978 Food Store Employer's Labor Council Philadelphia (Box 245, Folder 3)
- Railway Employees' Department of the American Federation of Labor w/ Duluth, South Shove and Atlantic Railway Company and Mineral Range Railroad Company 1927 (Box 245, Folder 4)
- Local 888 RCIA w/ Oxford Pendaflex Corp. 1975 (Box 245, Folder 5)
- Local 810, Steel, Metals, Alloys and Hardware Fabricators and Warehousemen aff. w/ International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America 1985-1988 (Box 245, Folder 6)
- Textile Workers Union of America w/ The Federation of Textile Representatives 1975 (Box 245, Folder 7)
- Transport Workers Union of America w/ Barnard College 1985-1988 Local 264 (Box 245, Folder 8)
- Transport Workers Union of America w/ Dynair Services, Inc. 1989-1991 (Box 245, Folder 9)
- Transport Workers Union of America Local 100 w/ Queens Transit Corp. and Steinway Transit Corp. 1959-1961 (Box 245, Folder 10)
- Transport Workers Union of American W/ Servair Inc. 1986-1988 (Box 245, Folder 11)
- District 2A Transportation, Technical, Warehouse Industrial and Service Employees Union w/ Princeton's NY Racing Security Service, Inc. 1987 (Box 245, Folder 12)
- Local No. 1 The Union of Flight Attendants w/ Continental Airlines Inc. 1977 (Box 245, Folder 13)
- United Assoc. of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry w/ Public Service Electric and Gas Company 1980 (Box 245, Folder 14)
- United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry w/ Public Service Electric and Gas Company 1984 (Box 245, Folder 15)
- United Assoc. of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting industry w/ Public Service Electric and Gas Company 1987 (Box 245, Folder 16)
- Local 259 United Workers of America and International Union. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America w/ Stamford Motors Inc., and Auto Lease of America 1982- 1985 (Box 245, Folder 17)
- United Auto Workers w/ Northern Michigan University 1973 (Box 245, Folder 18)
- Local 300 United Paperworkers International Union w/ Garden State Paper Company, Inc. 1979-1989 (Box 245, Folder 19)
- Local 300 United Paperworkers International Union w/ Garden State Paper Company, Inc. 1984 (Box 245, Folder 20)
- Utility Workers Union of America w/ Consolidated Edison Company of N.Y. Inc. 1975-1977 (Box 245, Folder 21)
- Local 210, Warehouse and Production Employees Union w/ Leo D. Bernstem and Sons Inc. 1987-1989 (Box 245, Folder 22)
- Actors' Equity 1996-1999 (Box 245, Folder 23)
- Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen 1979-1980 (Box 245, Folder 24)
- Food Drivers, Helpers and Warehousemen Local 500 1979-1982 (Box 245, Folder 25)
- Food Drivers, Helpers and Warehousemen Stal. Locals 500, 929, 420, and 676, 1971-1973 (Box 245, Folder 26)
- Highway Truck Drivers and Helpers Et, Al. Locals 17, 929, 470, and 676 (Box 245, Folder 27)
- Here Local 54 1979-1989 (Box 245, Folder 28)
- Hotel, Restaurant Employees and Bartenders' Union Local 224 1981-1984 (Box 245, Folder 29)
- Teamsters 1979-1985 (Box 245, Folder 30)
- ILGWU 1982-1985 (Box 245, Folder 31)
- International Union on Operating Engineering Local 542, 1978-1981 (Box 245, Folder 32)
- SEIU Local #36 1990-2000 (Box 245, Folder 33)
- United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners 1980-1983 (Box 245, Folder 34)
- United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners 1983-1986 (Box 245, Folder 35)
- United Food and Commercial Workers Local 56 1980-1983 (Box 245, Folder 36)
- United Paperworkers International Union Local 286 1972-1981 (Box 245, Folder 37)
- United Paperworkers International Union Local 375 1979-1982 (Box 245, Folder 38)
- United Paperworkers International Union Local 375 1975-1981 (Box 245, Folder 39)
- United Steelworkers of America 1976-1979 (Box 245, Folder 40)
- SEIU and UA Hospital 1974-1978 (Box 245, Folder 41)
- Newspaper Guild of Buffalo 1977-1987 (Box 245, Folder 42)
- Buffalo Newspaper Guild 1976 (Box 245, Folder 43)
- International Union of District 50, UMWWA, Local 12912, 1969-1972 (Box 245, Folder 44)
- United Glass and Ceramic Workers 1981-1984 (Box 245, Folder 45)
- International Brotherhood of Pottery and Allied Workers, 1971 (Box 245, Folder 46)
- American Postal Workers Union 1973-1981 (Box 245, Folder 47)
- Sheet Metal Workers Local 71 1978-1981 (Box 245, Folder 48)
- Buffalo Teachers Federation 1973-1978 (Box 245, Folder 49)
- Grand Island Teachers' Association 1977-1980 (Box 245, Folder 50)
- United Steelworkers 1974-1978 (Box 245, Folder 51)
- United Steel Workers 1971 (Box 245, Folder 52)
- United Steel Workers 1975 (Box 245, Folder 53)
- United Steelworkers 1982 (Box 245, Folder 54)
- United Steelworkers 1957-1958, 1957-1968 (Box 245, Folder 55)
- International Brotherhood of Boilermakers 1986 (Box 245, Folder 56)
- International Brotherhood of Papermakers 1952-1954 (Box 245, Folder 57)
- United Paperworks International Union 1978-1980 (Box 245, Folder 58)
- Retail Clerks International Association 1976-1979 (Box 245, Folder 59)
- United Food and Commercial Workers Union Retail Clerks Union Local 217 1981-1984 (Box 245, Folder 60)
- NYS Nurses' Association 1978-1980 (Box 245, Folder 61)
- Warehouse Union Local 6 1947-1953 (Box 245, Folder 62)
- International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Ironworkers Local 6 1972-1984 (Box 245, Folder 63)
- United Steelworkers 1982 (Box 246, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers 1976 (Box 246, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers 1980 (Box 246, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers 1974-1977 (Box 246, Folder 4)
- United Steelworkers 1972-1983 (Box 246, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers, 1962-1968 (Box 246, Folder 6)
- United Steelworkers 1971-1977 (Box 246, Folder 7)
- United Steelworkers 1980 (Box 246, Folder 8)
- United University Professionals, 1974-1988 (Box 246, Folder 9)
- Retail Clerks Union, Local 212 1976-1979 (Box 246, Folder 10)
- Retail Clerks Union, Local 212 1968-1971 (Box 246, Folder 11)
- Switchmen's Union of North America 1952 (Box 246, Folder 12)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen 1972 (Box 246, Folder 13)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen 1951 (Box 246, Folder 14)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers 1973 (Box 246, Folder 15)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees 1950 (Box 246, Folder 16)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees 1951 (Box 246, Folder 17)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees 1952 (Box 246, Folder 18)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees 1976 (Box 246, Folder 19)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees 1972 (Box 246, Folder 20)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees 1973 (Box 246, Folder 21)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees 1973 (Box 246, Folder 22)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees, 1951-1952 (Box 246, Folder 23)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees 1952 (Box 246, Folder 24)
- Machinist, Boilermaker; Sheet Metal Workers, Molders, Carmen, Electricians 1943-1952 (Box 246, Folder 25)
- Machinists, Boilermakers, Blacksmiths, Sheet Metal Workers, Electricians, Carmen 1949-1951 (Box 246, Folder 26)
- Machinists Boilermakers, Blacksmiths, Sheet Metal Workers, Electrical Workers and Carmen 1969 (Box 246, Folder 27)
- Railway Employees' Department 1949 (Box 246, Folder 28)
- Railway Employees Department 1949 (Box 246, Folder 29)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen 1946 (Box 246, Folder 30)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen 1950 (Box 246, Folder 31)
- Order of Railway Conductors 1930-1948 (Box 246, Folder 32)
- United Transportation Union 1971 (Box 246, Folder 33)
- Teamsters 1970-1976 (Box 246, Folder 34)
- Steven Sinker Donation, 1963-1967 (Box 246, Folder 35)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1979-1985 (Box 247, Folder 1)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1959-1985 (Box 247, Folder 2)
- I.L.G.W.U., 1967-1988 (Box 247, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Ladies Garment Cutters Union (I.L.G.W.U.), 1973-1991 (Box 247, Folder 4)
- I.L.G.W.U., 1973-1991 (Box 247, Folder 5)
- I.L.G.W.U., 1982-1994 (Box 247, Folder 6)
- I.L.G.W.U., 1994-1997 (Box 247, Folder 7)
- I.L.G.W.U., 1994-1997 (Box 247, Folder 8)
- ACTWU = American Federation of Government Employers, 1977-1985 (Box 248, Folder 1)
- AFSCME - Amherst Highway Employees Association, 1968-1983 (Box 248, Folder 2)
- UAW - Chevrolet 1961-1976 (Box 248, Folder 3)
- UAW - Chevrolet, UAW - Con Diesel 1973-1982 (Box 248, Folder 4)
- UAW - Ford 1941-1976 (Box 248, Folder 5)
- UAW - Ford 1982-1987 (Box 248, Folder 6)
- UAW - Ford. Buffalo Stamping 1970-1987 (Box 248, Folder 7)
- UAW - General Motors 1961-1970 (Box 248, Folder 8)
- UAW - General Motors 1967-1979 (Box 248, Folder 9)
- UAW - General Motors 1977-1982 (Box 248, Folder 10)
- UAW - General Motors, UAW - Roblin Industries 1968-1974 (Box 248, Folder 11)
- Bakery and Confectionaries, 1950-1952; Brewers 1946-1953 (Box 248, Folder 12)
- Brewers, 1950-1952 (Box 248, Folder 13)
- Bricklayers 1972; Buffalo and Western N.Y. Hospital 1977-1984; Buffalo Yerks Film 1974, 1972-1984 (Box 248, Folder 14)
- United Cements, Lime and Gypsum Workers 1950-1953 (Box 248, Folder 15)
- CSEA, 1977-1980 (Box 248, Folder 16)
- CSEA, Administrative Services Unit-NYS 1973-1988 (Box 248, Folder 17)
- CSEA, Institutional Services Unit-NYS 1973-1988 (Box 248, Folder 18)
- CSEA, Operational Services Unit-NYS, 1973-1988 (Box 248, Folder 19)
- CSEA, Professional, Scientific and Technical Service Unit-NYS 1972-1979 (Box 248, Folder 20)
- Communications Workers 1982-1996 (Box 249, Folder 1)
- Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers 1950 (Box 249, Folder 2)
- Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers 1951-1952 (Box 249, Folder 3)
- Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers 1966-1972 (Box 249, Folder 4)
- Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers 1973-1983 (Box 249, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers 1951-1973 (Box 249, Folder 6)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers 1971-1985 (Box 249, Folder 7)
- Electronic, Electrical, Technical, 1984-1987; Engineers and Architects 1951-1953, 1951-1987 (Box 249, Folder 8)
- International Association of Firefighters, 1969-1971; Foreman's Association 1950-1955, 1950-1971 (Box 249, Folder 9)
- Instrument Workers - Joint Crafts Council 1950-1982 (Box 249, Folder 10)
- International Association of Machinists 1947-1974 (Box 249, Folder 11)
- International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers 1970-1974 (Box 249, Folder 12)
- International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers 1972-1979 (Box 249, Folder 13)
- International of Machinists and Aerospace Workers 1977-1984 (Box 249, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Meat Cutters 1977-1980; United Mine Workers 1966-1969; International Union of Operating Engineers 1978-1981, 1966- 1981 (Box 249, Folder 15)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers 1964-1971 (Box 249, Folder 16)
- Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers 1968-1971 (Box 249, Folder 17)
- Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers 1969-1971 (Box 249, Folder 18)
- Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers 1971-1982 (Box 249, Folder 19)
- Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers 1980-1984 (Box 249, Folder 20)
- Independent Association or Plastic and Fiber Workers, 1985-1988; Public Employees Federation 1982-1995 (Box 249, Folder 21)
- RWDSU 1977-1978; United Rubber. Cork 1951-1979 (Box 249, Folder 22)
- Senate Professional Association 1971-1974; Journeymen Steamfitters 1975-1978; Svenska 1981-1982, 1971-1982 (Box 249, Folder 23)
- Teamsters 1976-1979; Upholsterers Upstate Telephone Employees 1963-1967, 1963-1979 (Box 249, Folder 24)
- Westinghouse Independent Salaries Unions 1950-1976 (Box 249, Folder 25)
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers United Paperworkers of America 1957 (Box 249, Folder 26)
- ILA Local 1286 with Archer-Daniels - Midway Co., 1937 (Box 250, Folder 1)
- ILA Local 1286, No Employer Listed, 1943 (Box 250, Folder 2)
- ILA Local 1286, No Employer Listed, 1944 (Box 250, Folder 3)
- ILA Local 1286, No Employer Listed 1945 (Box 250, Folder 4)
- ILA Local 1286 with Archer-Daniels-Midland Co. Delwood Elevator, 1946 (Box 250, Folder 5)
- Flour, Feed and Cereal Workers Union, Local 19184 with Archer-Daniel-Midland Co., 1946-1947 (Box 250, Folder 6)
- ILA Local 1286 w/ Archer-Daniels-Midland Co. Dellwood Elevator, 1947 (Box 250, Folder 7)
- Flour, Feed and Cereal Workers Union, Local 19184 with Spencer Kellogg and Sons, 1947 (Box 250, Folder 8)
- ILA Local 1286 with Commander-Larabee Milling Co., 1948 (Box 250, Folder 9)
- ILA Local 1286 with Archer-Daniels-Midland Company, 1953-1954 (Box 250, Folder 10)
- ILA Local 1286 with Archer-Daniels-Midland Co. Pension Agreement, 1954 (Box 250, Folder 11)
- ILA Local 1286 with Archer-Daniels-Midland Company, 1954-1955 (Box 250, Folder 12)
- ILA Local 1286 with Archer-Daniels-Midland Company, 1958-1961 (Box 250, Folder 13)
- AAA. American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) Agreements, 1994-2003 (Box 251, Folder 1)
- Airline Pilots Association; International. Agreements, 1996-2009 (Box 251, Folder 2)
- Air Traffic Controllers Association; National Agreements, 1998-2001 (Box 251, Folder 3)
- Air Craft Mechanics Fraternal Association. Agreements, 1974 (Box 251, Folder 4)
- Aluminum, Brick and Glass Workers International Union Agreements, 1996-2003 (Box 251, Folder 5)
- Asbestos Workers; International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators, and. Agreements, 1997 (Box 251, Folder 6)